Preliminary Guide to the Federation for American Immigration Reform (FAIR) records, 1867-2006 MS2195
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Working records, Circa 1965 - Circa 1999; Series 1
  - Testimony on census: Hagan, 1976 September 15; Series 1 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Testimony on census: Keane, 1985 September 18; Series 1 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Testimony on census: Noonan, 1985 September 18; Series 1 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Testimony on census: Passel, 1985 September 11; Series 1 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Testimony on census: Stein, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Texas Civil Liberties Union, 1987-1989; Series 1 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Unemployment and job displacement, undated; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Undocumented worker research, undated; Series 1 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Border partrol operations brief: McAllen Sector, undated; Series 1 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals: Rules and Procedures, 1988; Series 1 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - U.S. English, 1987-1989; Series 1 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - U.S. senate listing, undated; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Video case statement, 1987 November 12; Series 1 (Box 144, Folder 23)
  - Visas research, undated; Series 1 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Vote counts 1983, Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Votes in house 1982-1984, Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Votes in senate 1982-1984, Series 1 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - The Wardman Club, 1989; Series 1 (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - Ways and means committee (house), 1983; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Welfare, undated; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - White house domestic policy council, 1980; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - White house national agricultural lands survey, 1980; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - White house national security council, unknown; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - White house office of management and budget, 1979; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - White house President Ronald Reagan, 1980; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - White house program ideas, 1979-1981; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - White house Reagan administration FAIR interoffice memo, 1982; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - White house Reagan committee on immigration, 1980-1981; Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Whitman California Trip (1/2), 1993 March; Series 1 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - Whitman California Trip (2/2), 1993 March; Series 1 (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - Williams and Jensen, 1983-1987; Series 1 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Wisconsin speaker's bureau, undated; Series 1 (Box 146, Folder 10)
  - Witan, 1986 October 26-27; Series 1 (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - World bank atlas, 1986; Series 1 (Box 144, Folder 24)
  - Work authorization, 1985-1988; Series 1 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Work authorization, 1985-1988; Series 1 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Yearbook of American and Canadian Churches, 1988; Series 1 (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - 8 CFR 109: employment authorization, 1980; Series 1 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - 1982 congressional testimony, Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - 1983 congressional testimony, Series 1 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - 1990 Census adjustment, 1992; Series 1 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - 1990 Decennial census report, 1989; Series 1 (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - 2000 Census advisory committee, 1993 June 3-4; Series 1 (Box 144, Folder 9)
- Oral histories, 1989-2002; Series 2
  This series contains transcripts of oral histories of people involved in the founding and working of the Federation for American Immigration Reform. These oral histories date from 1989-2002.
  note: there is a separate oral history done with Garrett Hardin (not part of the FAIR project) at University of California at Santa Barbara.
  - Collins, Donald A. and Sarah Gamble Epstein, 2002 October 17; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Conner, Roger L., session one, 1989 January 27; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Graham, Otis L., Jr., 1990 February 19; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Hardin, Garrett, Ph.D., 1997 March 9; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Harte, Janet, 1997 January 31; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Lamm, Richard D., 1997 March 11; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Paddock, William C., 1993 February 28; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Rowland, Thad, 1991 February 2; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Stein, Dan, 1994 August; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Swensrud, Sidney, 1990; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Tanton, John H., M.D., 1989 April 20-21; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Publications, Circa 1979 - Circa 2000; Series 3
  This series contains publications produced and collected by the Federation for American Immigration Reform. The material dates from 1979-2000.
  - Action alerts, 1982-1984; Series 3 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Administrative law news, 1990; Series 3 (Box 128, Folder 12)
  - Alien employment controls, 1986; Series 3 (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - American attitudes towards immigration report, 1992 April; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - American bar association and human rights, 1990 Summer; Series 3 (Box 133, Folder 16)
  - American bar association journal, 1989 November; Series 3 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - American Immigration Lawyers Association monthy mailing, 1989 September - 1990 March; Series 3 (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - American Immigration Lawyers Association monthy mailing, 1990 May; Series 3 (Box 133, Folder 18)
  - American Immigration Lawyers Association newsletter, 1990 May; Series 3 (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - Border patrol articles, 1990; Series 3 (Box 146, Folder 7)
  - Cartoons: statue of liberty, 1980-1986; Series 3 (Box 134, Folder 18)
  - Center for immigration studies, 1986-1999; Series 3 (Box 134, Folder 20)
  - Congressional mailings, 1989; Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Congressional quarterly's editorial research reports, 1989 October 27; Series 3 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - Department of state consular affairs fraud prevention program overseas, 1989 August; Series 3 (Box 133, Folder 17)
  - Department of State semiannual report to congress, 1989; Series 3 (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - Discover total resources: a guide for nonprofits, 1985; Series 3 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Editorial, 1982-1987; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Eliminationa of Alienage Jurisdiction, 1989 November 16; Series 3 (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - Ellis Island: monument to America's immigrant heritage, undated; Series 3 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - FAIR annual report, 1992-1995, 1998; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - FAIR fifty million californians, 1991; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - FAIR immigration report: federation for american immigration newsletters, 1979-1990; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - FAIR legislative bulletin, 1983-1987; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - FAIR publications, undated; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Federal bar news and journal, 1989 November; Series 3 (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - Grant Writers Handbook, undated; Series 3 (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - Grant Writers Handbook, undated; Series 3 (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Houston journal of int'l law, article by Dan Stein (1/3), undated; Series 3 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Houston journal of int'l law, article by Dan Stein (2/3), undated; Series 3 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Houston journal of int'l law, article by Dan Stein (3/3), undated; Series 3 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Houston Lawyer article on IRCA, 1987 January - February; Series 3 (Box 139, Folder 12)
  - Immigration articles (1/4), 1989; Series 3 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Immigration articles (2/4), 1989; Series 3 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Immigration articles (3/4), 1989; Series 3 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Immigration articles (4/4), 1989; Series 3 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Immigration articles, 1990 October-November; Series 3 (Box 146, Folder 8)
  - Immigration articles, 1990 December - 1991 March; Series 3 (Box 146, Folder 9)
  - Immigration reform law institute watch, 1989; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Immigration reform law institute watch, 1989 October - 1990 May; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Immigration report, 1979 October - 1980 September; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Immigration report, 1979 October - 1984 February; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Immigration report, 1979 October; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Immigration report, 1979 November; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Immigration report, 1979 December; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Immigration report, 1980 October - 1981 September; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Immigration report, 1980 January; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Immigration report, 1980 February; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Immigration report, 1980 March; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Immigration report, 1980 April; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Immigration report, 1980 May; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Immigration report, 1980 June; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Immigration report, 1980 July; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Immigration report, 1980 August; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Immigration report, 1980 September; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Immigration report, 1980 October; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Immigration report, 1980 November; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Immigration report, 1980 December; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Immigration report, 1981 November - 1982 September; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Immigration report, 1981 January; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Immigration report, 1981 February; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Immigration report, 1981 March; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Immigration report, 1981 April; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Immigration report, 1981 May; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Immigration report, 1981 June; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Immigration report, 1981 July; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Immigration report, 1981 August; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Immigration report, 1981 September; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Immigration report, 1981 October; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Immigration report, 1981 November; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Immigration report, 1981 December; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Immigration report, 1982 January; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Immigration report, 1982 February; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Immigration report, 1982 March; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Immigration report, 1982 April; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Immigration report, 1982 May; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Immigration report, 1982 June; Series 3 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Immigration report, 1982 July; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Immigration report, 1982 July; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Immigration report, 1982 August; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Immigration report, 1982 September; Series 3 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Immigration report, 1982 October - 1983 September; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Immigration report, 1982 December - 1983 January; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Immigration report, 1983 February; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Immigration report, 1983 March; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Immigration report, 1983 April; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Immigration report, 1983 May; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Immigration report, 1983 June; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Immigration report, 1983 July; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Immigration report, 1983 August; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Immigration report, 1983 September; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Immigration report, 1983 October; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Immigration report, 1983 October; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Immigration report, 1983 October - 1984 September; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Immigration report, 1983 November; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Immigration report, 1983 December; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Immigration report, 1983 December; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Immigration report, 1984 March - 1987 August; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Immigration report, 1984 October - 1985 September; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Immigration report, 1984 January; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Immigration report, 1984 February; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Immigration report, 1984 March; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Immigration report, 1984 April; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Immigration report, 1984 May; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Immigration report, 1984 June; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Immigration report, 1984 July; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Immigration report, 1984 August; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Immigration report, 1984 September; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Immigration report, 1984 October; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Immigration report, 1984 November; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Immigration report, 1984 December; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Immigration report, 1985 December - 1986 December; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Immigration report, 1985 January; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Immigration report, 1985 February; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Immigration report, 1985 March; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Immigration report, 1985 July; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Immigration report, 1985 July; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Immigration report, 1985 August; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Immigration report, 1985 September; Series 3 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Immigration report, 1985 October; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Immigration report, 1987 January - March; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Immigration report, 1987 September - 1989 December; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Immigration report, 1988 October; Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Immigration report, 1988 November; Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Immigration report, 1988 December; Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Immigration report, 1989 January; Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Immigration report, 1989 February; Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Immigration report [1/2], 1989 March; Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Immigration report [2/2], 1989 March; Series 3 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Immigration report, 1989 July - August; Series 3 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Immigration report, 1990 January - 1992 November; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Immigration report, 1992 April - December; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Immigration report, 1993 January - December; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Immigration report, 1994 January - November; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Immigration report, 1995 February - December; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Immigration report, 1996 January - May; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Immigration report and members forum, 1992 November - 2000 April; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Information exchange, 1983-1988; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Information exchange, 1988 March 29; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Information exchange and reports, 1986 January 1; Series 3 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Internal newsletter, 1982; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - The International Teamster, 1987-1988; Series 3 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Landmark litigation report, 1989; Series 3 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Law Publications, 1989; Series 3 (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - Law review article (1/4), undated; Series 3 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Law review article (2/4), undated; Series 3 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Law review article (3/4), undated; Series 3 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Law review article (4/4), undated; Series 3 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Legislative bulletin, 1987; Series 3 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - National Right to Work legal defense foundation, inc., undated; Series 3 (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - Negative population growth, 1989; Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - News and publications, 1985 October; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - News and publications, 1985 November; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - News and publications, 1985 December - 1986 January; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - News and publications, 1985 December - 1986 January; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - News and publications, 1986 February; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - News and publications, 1986 March; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - News and publications, 1986 April; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - News and publications, 1986 May; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - News and publications, 1986 June; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - News and publications, 1986 August; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - News and publications, 1986 September; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - News and publications, 1986 October; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - News and publications, 1986 November; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - News and publications, 1986 December; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - News and publications, 1987 January; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - News and publications, 1987 February; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - News and publications, 1987 March; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - News and publications, 1987 April; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - News and publications, 1987 May; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - News and publications, 1987 June; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - News and publications, 1987 July; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - News and publications, 1987 August; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - News and publications, 1987 September; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - News and publications, 1987 October; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - News and publications, 1987 November; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - News and publications, 1987 December; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - News and publications, 1988 January; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - News and publications, 1988 February; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - News and publications, 1988 March; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - News and publications, 1988 April; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - News and publications, 1988 June; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - News and publications, 1988 July; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - News and publications, 1988 August; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - News and publications, 1988 September; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Newsletter, 1990 August-September; Series 3 (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - The Next Underclass: hispanic americans on the poverty treadmill, undated; Series 3 (Box 134, Folder 13)
  - Pew Charitable Trusts guidelines and procedures, 1989; Series 3 (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - PRUCOL: review article, undated; Series 3 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - PRUCOL: review article, undated; Series 3 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - PRUCOL: review article, undated; Series 3 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - PRUCOL: review article, undated; Series 3 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Publication and research program outline, 1983 February 2; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Report and Recommendations of the California fair employment and housing commission, 1989; Series 3 (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - Report of the Andrew W. Mellon Foundation, 1987; Series 3 (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - Report of the Alfred P Sloan Foundation, 1988; Series 3 (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Report of the Charles Stewart Mott Foundation, 1987; Series 3 (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - Report of the committee on immigration and nationality law, 1989 August; Series 3 (Box 133, Folder 12)
  - Report of the Ford Foundation, 1987; Series 3 (Box 132, Folder 10)
  - Report of the Lilly Endowment Inc, 1988; Series 3 (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - Report of the Pew Charitable Trust, 1987; Series 3 (Box 131, Folder 10)
  - Report of the Rockefeller Foundation, 1988; Series 3 (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - Report of the visa office, 1987; Series 3 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Report of the William and Flora Hewitt Foundation, 1987; Series 3 (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Report of the W.M. Keck Foundation, 1987; Series 3 (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - Shapers of the great debate on immigration, 1999; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Statistical yearbook of the INS, 1987; Series 3 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Various FAIR publications, 1992-2000; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Various FAIR publications, 1992-2000; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Various FAIR publications, 1992-2000; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - The Washington Lawyer, 1989 March-April; Series 3 (Box 133, Folder 14)
  - The Washington Lawyer, 1989 November-December; Series 3 (Box 133, Folder 13)
  - U.S. Carrying capacity, 1982; Series 3 (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - U.S. General Accounting Office report to congress on immigration reform, 1990 March; Series 3 (Box 132, Folder 11)
  - Weingart foundation annual report, 1988; Series 3 (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - The Young Lawyers Newsletter, 1988 February-March; Series 3 (Box 144, Folder 5)
- Legislation, 1910 - 1990; 1961-1990; Series 4
  This series contains legislative data related to the topic of immigration. The materials date from 1910-1990 with the bulk of records covering 1961-1990.
  - Act to form select commission on immigration and refugee policy (HR.12443), 1978; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Amendment to the immigration and nationality act (HR.2213), 1979; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Amendment to the internal revenue code of 1954 (HR.2214), 1979; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Amendment to the immigration and nationality act and the social security act (HR.2253), 1979; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Amendment to the immigration and nationality act (HR.4755), 1986; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Amendment to HR.2816, 1982; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Amerasian Children Relief Act of 1985, Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Bill: agricultural Program Ineligibility for Foreign Nationals (S.2310), 1986; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Bill: amend Internal Revenue Code of 1954 (S.2273), 1986; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Bill: amend Immigration and Nationality Act (HR.1379), undated; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Bill: amend immigration and nationality act (HR.1620), 1985; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Bill: amend Social Security (S.72), undated; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Bill: amend Social Security Act to Provide for Verification of Immigration Status (S.1215), 1985; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Bill: amend title 5 of U.S. Code (HR.1518), 1985; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Bill: authorize military on the border (HR.5048), 1986; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Bill: Cuban/Haitian Immigrant Status (HR.23), 1985; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Bill: current Census Data Used for Government Benefits (HR.258/HR.66), 1985; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Bill: deter immigration related marriage fraud (HR.3737), 1985; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Bill: deter immigration related marriage fraud (S.2270), 1986; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Bill: english language requirement exemption for elderly (S.1296), 1985; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Bill: foreign Labor Relief Under Countervailing Duty Laws (S.2311), 1986; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Bill: increase availability of immigrant visas (HR.107), 1979; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Bill: permit aliens with exceptional ability in business to be given third preference status (HR.1726), 1985; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Bill: permit Naturalization Courts to Retain Half of Fees Paid (HR.1410), 1985; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Bill: permit suspension of deporation (HR.1797), 1985; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Bill: provide equal treatment of father-child relationships as with mother-child relationships in the immigration process (HR.1725), 1985; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Bill: repeal provision excluding aliens on sole ground of sexual deviation (HR.2329), 1985; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Bill: reports and documents, undated; Series 4 (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - Bill: restrict Social Security to Aliens (HR.76), 1987; Series 4 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Bill: revise and reform immigration and nationality act (HR.1563), 1985; Series 4 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Border administration and security enhancement act, 1990; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Breaux amendment, 1980; Series 4 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - California regulations, 1982; Series 4 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Civil Rights Act, 1981; Series 4 (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Census legislative history, 1979-1987; Series 4 (Box 85, Folder 12)